casinolistings.com 2018-10-22

# Privacy Policy | Casino Listings

Casino Listings has created this privacy policy to demonstrate our commitment to respecting your privacy. Our information gathering and dissemination practices are disclosed below.

## Collection of Personal Information

You may be required to supply us with an email address in order to create an account at this website, or sign up for our newsletter. You may be asked for other relevant personal information to complete a purchase from our rewards shop. These are all optional features of this website and as such you do not have to supply us with any such information if you wish to browse this website anonymously.

_Casino Listings will never sell, trade, or pass on your personal information to any other third party, ever. We hate spam too._

If you would like a copy of the personal information we have on your account or would like to have your account closed, please contact us via our contact page.

### Children's Privacy

The Casino Listings website is intended for adults and we will not knowingly collect personal information from children under 18 years of age, or the legal age at which online gambling is permissable in your jurisdiction, whichever is greater. However we do not collect any personal information that would allow us to identify the age of a visitor to this site. If you are a parent or legal guardian of a child under this age who has become a member of this site, please contact us to notify us of a suspected violation.

## Web Logs and Browser Statistics

Information such as your IP address and web browser statistics may be logged while you access this site. We use this information in an aggregate form to help administer our server and improve our service.

### Cookies

Casino Listings uses a session cookie to maintain your current browsing session while logged in, and a persistent cookie to automatically log you in upon subsequent visits if you have an account with us. A persistent cookie is also used to preserve your country and currency preferences between visits, whether you are logged in or not. Cookies issued by this website do not contain any personally identifiable information and cannot be read by any other website.

## Third Party Advertising

Advertisements may be served on this website both from the CasinoListings.com domain and third party domains. In the course of serving advertisements to this site, a third-party advertiser may serve a cookie to your browser.

## Modifications to our Privacy Policy

Casino Listings reserves the right to change, at any time, at our sole discretion, this privacy policy. You are responsible for regularly reviewing our privacy policy. Your continued use of the services constitutes your acknowledgement of this policy. You may always view the latest privacy policy at https://www.casinolistings.com/privacy-policy.

This privacy policy was last updated on 22 May 2018.

## Contacting Us

If you have any questions or comments on our privacy policy, please contact us via our contact page.
